Mariah Mariah Mariah
Mor
that hurt huh what happened
and what's that bag doing there
no it can't be you mean that bag had a
Ah!
Oh, my God!
I ran over a cat! But how?
I didn't even see it lying there!
There was no way I could have
dodged the poor thing in time!
Exactly right! Huh?
That was just a bit of bad luck.
It's not like you meant to run it over.
Nah, if you want my take on the matter?
The real scoundrel here is the asswipe!
who left that poor kitten in a bag to die.
Pretty rotten, if you ask me.
We've got to do something!
Would it be the point?
You don't hear the little
furball meowing, do you?
It's dead.
So what's your name, kid?
I'm Tamami Kobayashi,
and I just happened to have graduated
from the same school you're attending.
Nice bike you got there.
So are you a freshman?
Yes, I am.
My name is Koichi Hirose.
Ah, high school.
Boy, that sure takes me back.
Good times.
At any rate, have a seat
over here, Mr. Hirose.
Uh... but... but I...
Come on, kid!
Quit that punk-ass quivering and sit down!
Now that you're nice and comfy,
I have a proposition for you.
I'll lay that pussycat to rest, and
you grease my palm with some cash.
Sound fair?
Hey!
There's something wrong with your ears!
What are you talking about?
Try to keep up!
This is serious business!
I know you're innocent and all,
but you're not planning to pull a
hit-and-run with my precious cat, are you?
You're saying that cat belonged to you?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Then aren't you the one who stuffed the
kitten inside a bag and
left it in the street?
Let's not get bogged down in details.
I'm asking if you think you're
gonna walk away from this scot-free.
After all, the killer
here is you, short stuff!
Let's go.
I bet you're feeling
pretty guilty right now,
but the good news is paying
a little fee could just
free yourself of that
oppressive feeling of guilt.
So why don't we begin the healing
by emptying out your wallet? Well?
Ah!
What is this thing?
It looks like some kind of freaky padlock!
And it's really heavy! Huh?
You're saying you could actually see it?
Ha!
What do you know?
That'll make things go
by a whole lot faster!
Wait, you mean this thing is a stand?
Why is a psycho stand
growing out of my body?!
Ah.
Hey Josuke, you seeing what I'm seeing?
It looks like Koichi's down there.
Yeah, that's Koichi, all right.
No doubt about it.
No matter where he goes, he always
seems to end up with the wrong crowd.
I'm sure he can handle himself.
Four months ago, I crossed paths with
a guy by the name of Keicho Nijimura,
and he gave me a pretty
handy special ability.
I hadn't a clue what was
happening, but it felt great.
And I figured if I put my
new powers to good use,
I'd never have to worry about a
thing for the rest of my life.
All right, cuff it up already.
Being cheap means the lock
stays right where it is.
And you wouldn't want that, would you?
I can't help you, really.
I'm flat broke.
Ah, then explain why you just looked away.
I didn't. I mean...
It got heavier!
Oh, no, I'm gonna...
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Didn't anybody ever teach
you that it's bad to lie?
Admit it or not, you know in
your heart that I'm right.
And the guiltier you feel, the bigger
and heavier that lock will grow.
The lock's size is proportional
to the weight of your guilt,
and the two are inexorably linked.
You can knock me out or
run a thousand miles away,
but you're never getting
rid of that thing.
So why don't you be a good
boy and give me your wallet?
How about it?
Didn't you say something
about being flat broke, kiddo?
This looks like 7,000 yen to me.
No, you can't!
That's the money I was going to use to
buy new sneakers for gym class today!
Whoa, sneakers?
You could go barefoot!
Hey, man.
What's going on? Huh?
Josuke and Okuyasu, you're here!
Looks like a grown man's
mugging a high school kid.
Why don't you get a job
and earn your own money?
Oh, butt out!
It's none of your business, so run along!
Sorry, that's not gonna happen.
Not when there's a stinking shitbag in
his dirty little stand in front of me.
I think it's time to take out the trash.
Hey, now!
Damn thing won't come off!
What kind of stand is this?
Hold on a sec.
You guys could see it, too?
How many of you freak shows are there?
You took the words right out of my mouth,
but the answer to that question can wait.
Till then, I'd appreciate it
if you'd remove that lock.
Hey, you assholes!
Don't you underestimate me!
Watch yourselves, because
I'm not fooling around here.
It's essential that criminals
pay for their crimes
in order to keep society
from crumbling around us.
If he's not going to pay, does that mean
one of you will cover what he owes me?
If so, I'll let you go.
Money's money, after all. Oh.
So you just want to get
your hands on our money.
I'd like to see you try.
Keep your guard up.
This loser already
swiped 7,000 yen from me.
That's because you lied
straight to my face, you dolt!
You really think that poor kitty's
life is only worth a measly 7,000 yen?
Well, think again.
You owe me 500 grand, kiddo!
500 grand?!
You bet your ass 500...
Would you please shut your hole?!
You did it, Okuyasu!
Yeah, but easy, man.
I've had it with your
bullshit, you bastard!
You're giving the run his
7,000 yen back right now!
Are we clear?
My front tooth!
Geez,
why the hell did you stumble around like
a drunk baby and make yourself fall over?
Make myself fall?
You're so mean!
How could you say such a
thing after hitting me?
My poor front tooth has been knocked out.
That's...
that's cruel.
Hey, wait a second.
You are okay, right?
No, stop, Okuyasu. It's a trap.
Whatever you do, don't let
him make you feel guilty.
He guilted you on purpose.
A front tooth will cost me a pretty
penny, and I don't have any insurance.
Damn, you little... Uh-oh!
I wouldn't do that if I were you!
If someone under my locks control
tries to hurt me in any way,
the damage will bounce back
and hurt my opponent instead!
Shit, you bastard!
Hey, about that kitten
you said Koichi ran over.
Would this happen to be it?
That's a stuffed animal.
Now, getting down to business.
I've got your tooth right here.
It's as good as new.
It's gone! Yeah, I know!
And I feel a million times lighter now!
Just who the hell are you?
Hey, did you forget about
the 7,000 you stole?
You win!
Here's the money!
Now hit the road before we
kick your smarmy little ass!
Oh, thank goodness.
He took the bills and only
left the corners behind.
He grabbed more than enough bills
to exchange them at the bank.
What a douchebag.
He'll pay, and it's not even my money.
Damn, easily 7,000 yen.
But they haven't gotten
rid of me that easily.
I'll get my revenge.
That rotten morning practically
ruined my entire day.
I'm glad it's over.
I'm home, police.
You didn't die, did you? Woof, woof!
Hey, Mom, I'm home from school.
Truth be told, I've heard
quite a lot about you, ma 'am.
Beautiful, kind, and so refined.
Oh, don't be silly.
No, it's all true.
Are you serious?
Cross my heart and hope to die.
Why is this guy in my house?
And why is he massaging
my mom's shoulders?
Hey, what is this?
And why are you here?
Hi, Ko.
Did you have a good day at school?
Come in.
I asked you a question!
Don't ignore me!
What are you doing here? Koichi,
this gentleman was kind enough to bring us
the money you dropped
on your way to school.
Huh?
7,000 yen, young man. Hold on!
This is unbelievable!
You told her you found it?
Well, of course!
After all, you did run into Mr.
Kobayashi on your bike today, didn't you?
What?
I just wanted to make sure you
got your money back, Koichi.
Yeah, it's the least you could do!
I don't understand.
Why are you getting so upset?
There's another thing I should address,
ma 'am, but it's not easy for me to say.
It would seem as though
I too dropped my wallet
when Koichi mowed me down
with his bike this morning.
Funny enough, it looks just like this one.
I figure in all the confusion earlier,
mine was taken in place of his.
Do you understand what
I'm getting at, ma 'am?
Think hard.
Uh, well, that seems like quite the
coincidence, but I suppose it's possible.
Well, there you go.
If you would please tell Koichi
to return my wallet immediately.
It had about 500,000 yen, give or take.
And I would like to be paid back in full.
Oh, good heavens! How much?
500,000?!
I get your game now, dirty con artist!
Ko, what happened?
You don't have to worry, Mom.
This guy is nothing but a fraud.
My, that's so rude!
I didn't want to bring it up,
but I have proof that your
son swiped my wallet for his.
I decided to eat at Johnny's last night,
where I ordered the hamburger meal.
And, oh, that's right!
I had a bowl of onion
Guardian soup on the side.
I believe it came out to 1,833
yen, but I could be wrong.
The receipt in the wallet Koichi
has should clear everything up.
He was telling the truth! No, he's not!
You have to believe me!
It's some kind of trick!
You planned it, didn't you?
Then you went out and bought
the same wallet to trick my mom!
He has quite the imagination,
but his habit of lying and stealing
is a disturbing character flaw.
Somebody here raised a real
delinquent as his mother.
Don't you feel any guilt over his actions?
That's enough!
Mom!
I was wondering when it would appear.
Now the weight of her guilt over her baby
boy turned criminal will oppress her soul.
I'm gonna bleed you dry, kid.
First, I'll take the house's land title
and seal, and we'll see what else you got.
I have to give it to you.
This is a great house.
Koichi, is something wrong?
Sis!
He got you too!
That's right, Ko.
When your lovely sister brought me tea,
I got her to spill some on my hand.
I wailed to make her think she burned me,
and you should have seen
how apologetic she was.
So sweet and seductive.
And she's a junior at an
all-girls school. Yummy.
Fully grown and ripe
for the pigging. Ha-ha!
Yah-yah-yah-hoo!
Huh?
What the bastard?
Mark my words, I'll make you pay for this.
Wait, what's going on?
What's that funny-looking
egg thing supposed to be?
Wait, what the hell is that?
Okay, you two, you need to
leave the room right now.
What's going on, Ko?
I've got this, but you have to be quiet.
I don't know what that thing
is, but get it away from me.
You may have gotten your mom
and sister out of the room,
but they're still my hostages.
And as long as they are, you have to
do what I say, so call off your beast.
Grrgh!
Hate to break it to you, buddy,
but you're not getting anywhere
near my mother or sister!
Fine!
Do you worse then, Keicho!
You think you're a Bites and just jimmy!
After you take the locks off my family!
You're a smart boy, Keicho!
Think about what it
would do to your mother
if she saw you beating the shit out of me!
Her guilt would be all-consuming
and swallow her up!
I told you to remove the locks now!
Who do you think you're talking
to, you sawed-off little dickhead?
I'm Tamami Kobayashi!
I'm not taking off the locks
until I'm good and ready!
Huh?
That punch?
It didn't hurt at all.
Hey, now.
What the hell was that?
Your friend's bark is a
lot worse than his bite.
What kind of stand is that, anyway?
As far as I can see, it's just a
poser without any speed or power!
How dare you scare me over nothing!
Screw you!
It's time I taught you a lesson.
A stand can have all the
potential in the world,
but it means nothing
without mental fortitude.
The hard truth is your feeble
spirit is weakening your stand.
But that just makes my feedback so much.
There's something weird on his cheek.
Ba and Ki, they're like
comic book sound effects.
What is this? What?
Where the hell is this
ringing coming from?
It's like the sound I heard
when he hit me before!
Ah!
Wait, what?
Why is there writing on my arm?
Dammit, it's stuck!
It won't come off!
There!
No, this can't be happening!
It's like the blasted sound
is coming from inside my body!
How could you stand out?
This guy's a power!
You little shit!
Stop this damn noise right now!
So that's it.
My stand is the ability to fill the body
with sound and turn it into a weapon.
Oh,
now that I think about it,
we studied a famous Matsuo Basho
poem just like this in school.
Something about the trill of the
locusts permeating through stone.
Damn!
How'd I let this dumb sucker get me?
All you have to do is take the locks off
my mom and sister and the noise will stop!
You can try resisting if you want to,
but who knows what effect the strain
will end up having on your body.
Knock off the ring!
Stop trying to be a tough guy
and take the locks off my family!
Damn you!
A pitiful bug like you has no
right to act so high and mighty!
The reason I'm such a boss-ass conman is
because I don't cave
in to upstart pizzants!
I'm Tamami, and the Taba stands for balls!
So you're about to see how big mine are!
I'm not scared of that
knife or your tiny balls!
Keep underestimating me!
I'll show you a whole new
world of horror and pain!
Here comes the agony of the padlock!
What?!
Oh my god, no! Ko!
Not only is the cut shallow, but the
pain and panic is fake! Toss! Toss?
Who's screaming?
What's going on in here?
Ko? No!
You've got it wrong!
Shit!
The lock's got bigger! Yes!
Ko! Why, son?
How could you do this?
Where did I go wrong?
Don't believe it!
Please, Mom!
You have to know I didn't do this!
Sis!
I'm the winner!
Told you you couldn't beat me!
Now hurry up and get rid of this
racket, Koichi, or your mom's gonna die!
Don't just stand there!
Do you want the guilt to
cross your mom into a pancake?
Although,
when a person is wracked with this much
guilt, death seems like a sweet release.
That's it.
I can't take it.
It's over! Mom, don't! No more!
I can't live like this!
Your turn to stop being a tough guy!
Next to sound, you're gonna watch your
mom paint the room with her blood!
Actually, I don't think I will.
Here's a better idea.
I'll make it worse!
Believe me!
What?
Mom, I'm telling the truth!
Believe me!
Believe!
Please, Mom.
She's too far gone!
She'll never believe you!
Believe!
Come on. Koichi.
If his own mother won't
believe him, then who will?
I have to have faith in my darling boy.
He's always been such a perfect angel.
He'd never hurt a soul.
And I know in my heart
he'd never steal. Yes!
This isn't good!
Mom!
It's not possible.
Parents never trust their brats.
At least mine never trusted me.
So what makes him special?
Shit!
I was only joking!
Please, Ko, surely you wouldn't
kill a guy over a joke, would ya?
Take the lock off my sister, too.
I've already taken care of it.
I could never do anything to
harm such a picturesque face.
And so you know, I was only
kidding about taking your house.
I even gave you back all
of your yen. See? Joke!
Please have mercy on me!
I'll do anything, Master Kawichi!
Really?
You'll do anything I want?
Yes! Just name it!
I'll be your personal underling!
All right.
Works for me.
Your first duty is to bring
me 500 grand by tomorrow.
Take it easy.
Can't you recognize your
joke when you hear one?
That didn't sound like a joke to me.
Uh, hey, Okuyasu, is it just me
or is that guy really creepy?
Master, allow me to carry your bag.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Oh, of course I do.
Master Koichi, you're a true
man among men! Aw, shucks.
You don't have to buy - I swear,
it's like we're in the Twilight Zone.
I don't know what that means, but my brain
hurts just watching all this weirdness.
Anytime I need to see a
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taken to a base
with a crystal mine.
A magenta feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a chicken cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the humic and the ball that I need to.
I want to.
Come stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you?
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I got to find out.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I got to find out.